

#### Profile

Junior Front-end developer. I finished a number of GoIT courses and successfully accomplished several pet projects. I have used core JS, React, Redux. I've also mastered HTML5 & CSS3.

I have basic experience with build tools (Webpack, Babel and Gulp), experience with agile methodology and working within Jira and Trello. I have a working knowledge of Adobe Photoshop.

I have experience in conducting communications with English native speakers in both written and verbal form.

## **Employment History**

Beta QA at Nova Pochta, Kiev

January 2017 — May 2017

Designing and performing positive and negative test cases to ensure compliance with the customers' requirements

Working with test management system TestRail

Documented issues in the bag tracking system JIRA

# Manager of technical operations at Partner Communications Company Israel

March 2006 — June 2012

Define and manage professional services for customers.

Translate customer needs assessments for complex implementations.

Manage relationship with vendor support services team.

Provide knowledge and training on products to the internal team.

## Education

#### GoIT, Kiev

February 2018 — October 2019

Full stack Certificate (HTML+CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node.js)

#### Yurij Chernigorcev IT-school, Kiev

January 2017 — April 2017

Software testing Certificate, 2017

### College of Management, Israel

January 2005 — January 2006

Certified management and accounting

#### **Details**

0991209873

larysa.skrypkin@gmail.com

#### Links

Resume

#### **Skills**

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

React

Redux

Adobe Photoshop

GitHub

## Languages

English

Hebrew